CHRISTIAN LEON

IT Support

Contact Information

(201) 491-1112

Christianleon0224@gmail.com

GitHub:

cdl9.github.io

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/christian-daniel-leon/

Skills

- Customer Service
- Technical Support
- Management Services

Languages

- English
- Spanish
- French

Experienced professional with 6 years of managing departments, directing training, as well as, overseeing computer configuration. Skilled in troubleshooting Windows terminals, providing technical support, and managing services to ensure smooth operations. Strong background in customer service, technical support, and incident documentation.



Employment History

Staffing Manager Jan 2022 - Present

Exquisite Staffing • new york

- Manages the department in charge of scheduling over 400 employees across multiple locations.
- Directs the training of new staff members monthly.
- File management and daily documentation of incidents and reports.

IT Assistant Aug 2018 - Present

Exquisite Staffing • new york

- Performs troubleshooting for Windows terminals
- Oversees computer configuration and provides training to end-users on how to use the company's specific software.

Software Developer Intern Jan 2021 - May 2021

AnalytIQ • new jersey

- Worked on the design and development of a cross-platform app using React Native, React, and hosted it on Microsoft Azure
- Collaborated on the creation of a new MySQL database to connect the web and mobile app



Education

B.S Computer Science

New Jersey Institute of Technology • Newark, NJ

A.S Computer Science

Hudson County Community College • Jersey City, NJ



Certifications

Google IT Support Professional Certificate

Google UX Design Professional Certificate